Come on, brother.
You have a problem with your wife.
Come out!
Your wife wants to leave you.
Testimony Time
My name is Augustine Igbinovia.
I'm from Edo State, Nigeria, but I reside in South Africa.
Last week Sunday. I was inside this church, sitting by this side
when the man of God called me out and prophesied that I have a problem in my marriage.
I confirm that prophecy to be a hundred percent true.
I have a problem in my marriage as a result of unfaithfulness due to the spirit of lust.
I have been unfaithful to my wife.
I indulged myself in communicating on social media via my phone.
At the beginning, I didn't go outside.
My wife was suspecting me because I was always on my phone.
As the result of the spirit of lust, I developed the spirit of anger.
Any time my wife accused me of doing something that I was not supposed to do in the marriage,
I ended up being angry. And most of the times I'd beat her up and she'd call the cops on me.
The spirit of lust entered me after I got married.
The spirit of lust entered me through communicating on social media.
My wife was unhappy. The spirit of lust caused me to beat my wife on two occations.
On the third time, she called the police, and I was given a protection order for me not to come close to her.
We have been separated for eight months now.
This is the letter of the protection order,
and this is my divorce summon, issued to me by my wife's lawyer.
Okay.
After the problems in my marriage, my wife told me to go to The SCOAN.
Until I got my deliverance, or until the man of God invited her, the marriage would be over.
Man of God, most of the time, I reacted towards my wife with anger which was due to my past relationship.
I had a 10-year relationship prior to this marriage - with a lady I was supposed to get married to.
Despite everything I did for her...
Your wife has how many children for you?
One, sir. One daughter, sir.
I think they are here now. Let her come out.
The more he talks, the more he provokes the Spirit of God.
It's better we do not hear from you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Mr & Mrs Augustine Igbinovia
Prophecy Confirmation
I want to thank you very much.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
After the deliverance here on Sunday and listening to what he was saying,
I realised that there was a need for me to give a call to our sister.
I had to call her. I was the one who spoke with you.
Thank you for honouring this call.
Thank you, Sir.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
She knows what it means to marry and what marriage means.
She is a godly person.
No matter what happened, we need to know God's opinion. That is why she is here.
Not that there's a special thing in you. You just have that zeal for God.
Marriage is not a hobby.
This is a relationship.
We need to meet the father of relationship - God -
for whatever happened in a relationship. That is why she is here.
My sister, this is a marriage from God.
I want to assure you. After the meeting here, I will sit with you people.
He will write a note. He will sign.
He is a bad bad boy. That's all. I will not say more than that. He is a bad boy.
God says, Give him another try. Simple.
He's a bad boy, but that boy has been delivered.
He can still go back to being bad because you have your life.
There is nothing we can do.
God has delivered you. You can still choose to go back to that bad life.
But he is a bad boy. I will not say more than that.
So, thank you very much, my daughter.
After the meeting, I'm going to meet you.
Don't bother to say anything. Anything you say will scatter our reconciliation.
We don't want to hear anything.
Please give thanks to God. God says you should give him another chance.
So give him another chance.
I will not say...
This is the presence of God.
I will not stand here and because I'm a Nigerian and you are a Nigerian, I will begin to say...
We are saying the mind of God.
Give thanks to God: "God, we thank You for giving me another chance".
Give this man another chance.
Thank Him because of your wonderful child.
Thank you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
My name is Mpho Igbinovia.
I'm a banker by profession. I'm from South Africa.
I would like to thank the man of God for his words.
I'd also like to thank him for inviting me here.
He provided everything - from the ticket to fly here, the accommodation, and the food.
Thank you very much, Man of God. I will honour your words as I have always done. Thank you, Sir.
You can give thanks to God for giving you another chance.
Man of God, I want to say thank you for reconciling my marriage
and for letting God use you to give me another chance in my marriage.
I promise never to go back to my old ways.
Okay. Thank you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Thank you.
Can you just...
Mr & Mrs Augustine Igbinovia
Prophecy Confirmation
You will see that he is the one that hates to do that.
Mr & Mrs Augustine Igbinovia
Prophecy Confirmation
Thank you very much. Thank you, my daughter. Thank you. Thank you very much.
Standard for Life
My name is Augustine Igbinovia.
I'm a Nigerian from Edo State, residing in South Africa.
The lady beside me is my lovely wife, Mrs Mpho Igbinovia from South Africa.
You're welcome, Sir. Can you just tell us - since you're coming to The SCOAN,
what God Almighty has done for you, especially in the area of your marriage.
I want to first thank God and thank Prophet T.B. Joshua
for reconciling my marriage and bringing back peace to my home.
I'm the one the man of God prophesied about who had a problem in his marriage due to the spirit of lust.
I want to say, Thank You, God and thank you, Prophet T.B. Joshua,
for bringing back peace to my home and restoring my marriage.
The man of God said that I have a lovely wife.
He also said that I should make sure not to go back to my old ways.
He asked me to write an undertaking that I have written to the man of God, stating my promise to him.
This is my promise, undertaking letter to God and to the man of God as well
that I'll never go back to my old ways.
I read: I, Augustine Igbinovia, 32 years of age, from Edo State, Nigeria,
would like to thank the man of God, Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua for reconciling my marriage.
And I promise God and him that I will never go back to all the bad and negative ways I have been living my life.
And I want God to give me the grace and strength to keep my promise in Jesus' name.
This letter was signed by me on the 14th of March 2017 at 12:24 am.
This is an undertaking that the man of God has asked me to write,
stating that I promise never to go back to my old ways.
And if I go against what I've written here, whatever happens is left for me to answer.
We give glory to God that you are here today with your wife at The SCOAN.
So since the word of prophecy you received last week during the prayer,
can you just tell us the changes you've witnessed in your life?
I can say that I have found total peace.
Since Sunday, I've found peace with myself.
The spirit of lust totally left me.
How do you know that the spirit of lust has left you?
I know because before, whenever I saw a lady, I'd lust after her.
But since my deliverance and the prophecy from the man of God,
I no longer feel that way anymore, and the spirit of lust has left me.
You're standing next to your wife now. What do you want to say to her?
I want to apologise to my wife for the wrong things I have done in the past.
I promise to stay faithful to her in this marriage
And I promise to love her like never before.
My name is Mpho Igbinovia from South Africa.
The man standing next to me is my wonderful husband.
The man of God told me that I and my husband need to stay steadfast in prayer.
He told me that I need to monitor him as a wife, to make sure that he doesn't go back to his old ways.
We saw your husband reading an undertaking,
confirming that he has promised God not to return to his past. What can you say?
I accept the undertaking and I thank the man of God for making him understand
the importance of him following what he should or shouldn't do.
I'm very happy and pleased
and I pray that God strengthens him so that he will not go back to his old ways.
Amen. We thank Jesus Christ.
Just in the little time you've been in here in The SCOAN,
what are the the changes that you've witnessed just in this short time?
My husband is more laughing now. Just like it was in the beginning.
He is showing love to both me and his family as well.
So, I can surely say that slowly but surely he is showing the signs that he has changed.
We thank Jesus Christ.
You mentioned that you've actuallly filed for divorced.
We saw the divorce letter that was being held up on Sunday.
In the light of what God has done for you here, what is your decision concerning this?
My decision is that I am definitely going to honour the words of the man of God
because I believe that through him, God speaks.
I will definitely call off the divorce as I also want to work things out with my husband.
Thank God, Madam. We'd like to ask you in the light of what you have received here in The SCOAN,
and the counsel of Prophet T.B. Joshua that he has given to you,
what is your word of advice to viewers around the world, especially to married couples?
I would like to tell them that as Prophet T.B. Joshua always says,
it's always good to run to God and not to anybody else.
We all know that the devil does not like places where love exists
so we need to shame the devil and make sure that whatever situation,
whatever troubles that you might be going through,
you need to make sure that you run to God and not to anybody else.
In life, there are many voices that one can hear.
T.B. Joshua always says that we must listen to the voice of God,
not to the voice of your friends or family or the voice of the devil.
Listen to the voice of God.
My advice to viewers all around the world, both married and unmarried:
If you find yourself moving from a hurtful relationship to the next relationship.
I want you to allow God to release you first before you move into the next relationship
because if you carry the pain from the past relationship into your new relationship, like I did,
you will likely end up experiencing the same thing as I have experienced in my marriage.
You mean to say in your own case, you carried pain of a past relationship
into this marriage and that really affected the marriage.
Yes, in my own case, I carried the pain of my past relationship into my marriage
and it truly affected me.
I want to apologise to my wife who has been suffering from my pain of the past.
I want to advise every viewer to make God's Word the standard of their life and their marriage.
Amen. Thank You, Jesus. We want to encourage this couple to continue to stay close to Jesus Christ
and we believe the two of you will come back here with more wonderful testimonies,
now that God Almighty has come into this matter, and we know the best is yet to come, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Thank You, Jesus.
Mr & Mrs Augustine Igbinovia
Prophecy Confirmation